A Guide to the Mills E. Godwin for Governor Campaign reports of campaign contributions and expenditures, 1973-1974
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Mills E. Godwin for Governor Campaign reports of contributions and expenditures, 1973-1974
The Library of Virginia
28182
.45 cu. ft. and 1 box
Mills E. Godwin for Governor Campaign
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mills E. Godwin, 9th Street Office Building, Richmond, Virginia.
Custodial History
Accession 28165 is filed with accession 28182
Historical Information
Republican candidate Mills E. Godwin (1914-1999) defeated Democratic candidate Henry E. Howell (1920-1997) in the 1973 contest for the office of Governor of Virginia in one of the closest races in Virginia history. This was Godwin's second election to the governorship, having also won election in 1965.
Scope and Content
Reports, 1973-1974, of campaign contributions and expenditures for the Mills E. Godwin's (1914-1999) 1973 gubenatorial campaign. Includes financial reports from Godwin's statewide campaign and for groups and organizations financially supporting his candidacy.
Contents List
- Statement by Mills E. Godwin, 24 October 1973 (Folder 1)
- Circular letter to chairmen regarding disbursements, 24 October 1973 (Folder 2)
- Schedule of receipts (covering 11 November 1972 to 15 October 1973), 24 October 1973 (Folder 3)
- Schedule of receipts (covering 27 August-23 October 1973), 24 October 1973 (Folder 4)
- Disbursements, 24 October 1973 (Folder 5)
- Contractors for Godwin, 24 October 1973 (Folder 6)
- Virginia Dentists for Godwin, 24 October 1973 (Folder 7)
- Physicians for Godwin, 24 October 1973 (Folder 8)
- Things...on loan, 24 October 1973 (Folder 9)
- Statement by Mills E. Godwin, 5 December 1973 (Folder 10)
- Report on contributions and expenditures, 5 December 1973 (Folder 11)
- Report on contributions and expenditures (local committees), 5 December 1973 (Folder 12)
- Air transportation and contributions in kind, 5 December 1973 (Folder 13)
- Schedule of receipts, 5 December 1973 (Folder 14)
- Schedule of disbursements, 5 December 1973 (Folder 15)
- New Car Dealer Committee for Godwin, 5 December 1973 (Folder 16)
- Virginians for Godwin, 5 December 1973 (Folder 17)
- Report of campaign and election contributions and expenditures, 6 December 1973-4 January 1974 (Folder 18)